{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_15_4QIJ8P",
                "player_9_4QIJ8P",
                "player_12_4QIJ8P",
                "player_4_4QIJ8P"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                15,
                9,
                12,
                4
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    13806.93,
                    -3095.951,
                    198.4,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    13736.156,
                    -2934.509,
                    198.15,
                    0,
                    -162.86669228865563,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    13930.078,
                    -2500.187,
                    198.105,
                    0,
                    73.85296959762707,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    13920.393,
                    -2810.727,
                    198.15,
                    0,
                    -57.70527189754833,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            14374.311,
            -2921.795,
            198.15
        ],
        "sample_radius": 838.2816383235527
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            13477.202,
            -2188.576,
            198.135,
            0,
            -60.14802267479128,
            0
        ],
        [
            14045.148,
            -3664.679,
            198.135,
            0,
            103.34659842165358,
            0
        ],
        [
            14316.476,
            -2434.113,
            197.917,
            0,
            -139.39771497576683,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many figures in the scene are in an upright or active posture?",
                "answer": "Three"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are characterized by a lack of hair on their head?",
                "answer": "One"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many of the people present are *not* wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "Four"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many male figures in the scene are *not* bald?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What is the total count of individuals who have either a medium or black skin tone?",
                "answer": "Three"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many humans are engaged in an action other than standing or lying down?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Excluding the person who is lying down, how many other distinct postures are observed among the figures?",
                "answer": "Three"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are female?",
                "answer": "One"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What is the state of the bald man in the brown sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. hold_object",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. sit",
                    "D. crouch"
                ],
                "answer": "A. hold_object"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. hold_object",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. walk",
                    "D. hold_object"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. sit",
                    "D. crouch"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            }
        }
    }
}